<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on Microdream</title>
    <link>https://lsal.me/categories/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on Microdream</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-Hans</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 08:09:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lsal.me/categories/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>000083</title>
      <link>https://lsal.me/posts/000083/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 08:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lsal.me/posts/000083/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be an emperor. That&amp;rsquo;s not my business. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to rule or conquer anyone. I should like to help everyone, if possible, Jew, gentile, black man, white. We all want to help one another. Human beings are like that. We want to live by each other&amp;rsquo;s happiness — not by each other&amp;rsquo;s misery. We don&amp;rsquo;t want to hate and despise one another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this world there is room for everyone. And the good earth is rich and can provide for everyone. The way of life can be free and beautiful, but we have lost the way. Greed has poisoned men&amp;rsquo;s souls, has barricaded the world with hate, has goose-stepped us into misery and bloodshed. We have developed speed, but we have shut ourselves in. Machinery that gives abundance has left us in want. Our knowledge has made us cynical. Our cleverness, hard and unkind. We think too much and feel too little. More than machinery we need humanity. More than cleverness we need kindness and gentleness. Without these qualities, life will be violent and all will be lost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aeroplane and the radio have brought us closer together. The very nature of these inventions cries out for the goodness in men, cries out for universal brotherhood, for the unity of us all. Even now my voice is reaching millions throughout the world — millions of despairing men, women and little children — victims of a system that makes men torture and imprison innocent people. To those who can hear me, I say — do not despair. The misery that is now upon us is but the passing of greed — the bitterness of men who fear the way of human progress. The hate of men will pass, and dictators die, and the power they took from the people will return to the people and so long as men die, liberty will never perish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soldiers! Don&amp;rsquo;t give yourselves to brutes — men who despise you — enslave you — who regiment your lives — tell you what to do — what to think or what to feel! Who drill you, diet you, treat you like cattle, use you as cannon fodder. Don&amp;rsquo;t give yourselves to these unnatural men — machine men with machine minds and machine hearts! You are not machines! You are not cattle! You are men! You have the love of humanity in your hearts. You don&amp;rsquo;t hate! Only the unloved hate — the unloved and the unnatural!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soldiers! Don&amp;rsquo;t fight for slavery! Fight for liberty! In the 17th Chapter of St. Luke it is written: &amp;ldquo;the Kingdom of God is within man&amp;rdquo; — not one man nor a group of men, but in all men! In you! You, the people have the power — the power to create machines. The power to create happiness! You, the people, have the power to make this life free and beautiful, to make this life a wonderful adventure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, in the name of democracy, let us use that power! Let us all unite!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— Charlie Chaplin, The Great Dictator&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>000076</title>
      <link>https://lsal.me/posts/000076/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 08:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lsal.me/posts/000076/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;最近听歌总是听到些有年头的歌。原来初听起，总觉得俗套，而现在却没出息地一个个点红心。借用歌词：“只能靠一首歌真的在说我。”只能说当时太年轻吧。反而又想，现在不也是很年轻，对于感情的事情拿起放下搞不明白，日后或又有其他烦恼。耳光乐队的《鸿鹄志》倒真扇了一记警钟。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>000069</title>
      <link>https://lsal.me/posts/000069/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 15:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lsal.me/posts/000069/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;独行万里，所欲所求，都是过客。心上无那许多牵绊，反倒自由了。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>000063</title>
      <link>https://lsal.me/posts/000063/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 02:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lsal.me/posts/000063/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;听到 Stand By Me 的时候，还想起了 Hakuna Matata 。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://music.163.com/#/song?id=21615671&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Stand By Me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>000046</title>
      <link>https://lsal.me/posts/000046/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 10:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lsal.me/posts/000046/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;一天下来十分疲惫，晚上看了看 ZeroNet，曾经热闹的博客或论坛都许久没有人更新了，零网的潮水似乎退去。贴子日期里 “2017” 这个曾经很新鲜的数字，现在看起来又很老旧。我想起了东先生，两月前才在推特上知道他离开人世的消息，随未深交但有伤感，时常想起，唏嘘感叹起来。或许也是因为这个原因，我选择重回零网，面对无可预料的未来，在当下给自己一个留存的回忆。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;衰退的零网中文圈让我的心情有些不太爽朗，但又想起了这首歌，虽然听上去有消极感，但我愣是在那种“有人与我有同样的感觉”的想法下听淡了孤独。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>000043</title>
      <link>https://lsal.me/posts/000043/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 10:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lsal.me/posts/000043/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;听到一首歌，叫 shelter 。旋律尚可，让我着迷的是歌曲封面。是我儿时想象里遮风蔽雨，拥抱温暖壁炉的住所。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>000033</title>
      <link>https://lsal.me/posts/000033/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 01:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lsal.me/posts/000033/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;好了，好了，我不再挣扎了，拥抱和享受吧。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://riccolabel.bandcamp.com/album/embracing-the-universe&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Embracing the Universe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>000032</title>
      <link>https://lsal.me/posts/000032/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 07:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lsal.me/posts/000032/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;没有承诺的时候，也不必惊慌失措了。该来的都来吧，该走的也走吧。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://music.163.com/#/song?id=407002789&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Welcome To The Show&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>000017</title>
      <link>https://lsal.me/posts/000017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 12:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lsal.me/posts/000017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;莫名想起八年前的事情。长大了才知道过去多么美好，这个必然的过程真是让人痛心呢。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>000016</title>
      <link>https://lsal.me/posts/000016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 07:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lsal.me/posts/000016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;想明白了一件事情：不需要挣扎的时候，不要挣扎。放弃了必胜的信念，放弃了失败的想法，释放了焦虑，一身轻松，效率出乎意料地变高。有些时候，上天自有安排，我且快乐地做事，快乐地生活。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>000015</title>
      <link>https://lsal.me/posts/000015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 06:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lsal.me/posts/000015/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Human beings are terrible messes, Andrew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>000009</title>
      <link>https://lsal.me/posts/000009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 13:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lsal.me/posts/000009/</guid>
      <description>一是感觉现在再努力有点晚，二是纷纷扰扰的事情太多。但还是要靠自己才能静下心来。无忧无虑地前进吧。 分享一首：</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>000006</title>
      <link>https://lsal.me/posts/000006/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 12:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lsal.me/posts/000006/</guid>
      <description>今天一直在脑中回放 Adam Lambert 的 Whataya Want From Me，后来索性戴耳机单曲循环了一个下午，莫名听出许多了悲伤和孤独。晚上墙又高了些，前路不可期。浮世果真如倒影。</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>